Moore, Frank C.; Papers apap223
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Speeches, 1934-1969; 10; 10 cubic ft.
  - Speeches, 10.37 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. Past Village Officials Dinner. Albion Marti's, 10/03/1951
    - b. University of Buffalo - Law Class Reunion, Buffalo Athletic Club, 10/04/1951
    - c. Newburgh Chamber of Commerce Dinner. Hotel Newburgh, 10/10/1951; 2 copies
    - d. Schoharie County Rally. Schoharie, N.Y., 10/11/1951
    - e. Delaware County - Wide Women's Republican Dinner, Sidney, 10/15/1951
    - f. Senator Stanley Bauer Testimonial Dinner, 10/17/1952
    - g. Empire State Association of Commerce. Albany, N.Y., 10/18/1951
    - h. Central Zone, N.Y.S. Teachers Assn. Syracuse - War Memorial Aud, 10/19/1951
    - i. New York State School Boards Assn. War Memorial Auditorium, Syracuse, 10/22/1951
    - j. League of Women Voters Troy, N.Y. - Old GYM. R.P.I., 10/26/1951; 3 copies
    - k. Speech - Buffalo Teachers Federation. Hotel Statler, Buffalo, 11/03/1951
    - l. New York State Region. U.S. NTL Student Assn. Assembly Chamber, Albany, 11/09/1951
    - m. Speech - N.Y.S. Teachers Association House of Delegates Dinner, Hotel Seneca Rochester, N.Y., 11/19/1951; 2 copies
    - n. Speech - Thanksgiving Day Community Church Service, St. John's Church, Buffalo, N.Y., 11/22/1951
    - o. Speech - Dedication of West Seneca School - Kenmore, N.Y., 11/14/1951
    - p. Speech - National Inst. Of Municipal Law Officers, N.Y.C. - Roosevelt Hotel, 11/29/1951
  - Speeches, 10.38 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
    - a. Speech - St. Andrew's Society Dinner. Waldorf - Astoria Hotel - N.Y.C., 11/30/1951
    - b. Speech - New York State Conservation Council, Inc. Buffalo, N.Y., 12/08/1951; 3 copies
    - c. Speech - University of Buffalo. Niagara Frontier Convocation, Buffalo, N.Y., 12/08/1951; 6 copies
    - d. Speech - Yonkers, Dedication of School, 12/10/1951
    - e. Penn Yan, Barden Testimonial Dinner, 12/17/1951
  - Speeches, 10.39 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
    - a. Speech - New York State Bar Association Municipal Branch - N.Y.C., 01/24/1952
    - b. AEX, Robert Testimonial Dinner Rochester - Elks Clun, 01/31/1952
    - c. University of Buffalo Conference on Local Gov. Buffalo Athletic Club - Road Map For Local Gov. Lawyers, 02/05/1952; 8 copies
    - d. Time Square Club, Hotel Astoria Afternoon, N.Y.C., 03/23/1952
    - e. University of Rochester - Management Clinic, 04/21/1952
    - f. Speech - Mock Senate - Albany Assembly Chamber, 04/05/1952
    - g. Allegany Central School Dedication - Allegany, N.Y., 04/19/1952
  - Speeches, 10.40 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Annual Meeting N.Y.S. Assessor's Association. Albany, N.Y. Ten Eyck Hotel, 04/24/1952; 9 copies
    - b. Speech - Testimonial Dinner For Nathanial L. Goldstein, Waldorf - Astoria NYC Medical School Campaign, Yeshiva University, 05/01/1952
    - c. Bronx Rotary Club Speech On Benjamin Franklin, 05/06/1952; 4 copies
    - d. Pace College Commencement Address. New York City, 06/20/1952
    - e. Queens College - Flushing, N.Y., Commencement Address, 06/18/1952; 4 copies
    - f. N.Y.S. Health Conference. Olympic Arena, Lake Placid, N.Y., 06/04/1952; 3 copies
    - g. New York State's Public Administration Training Program. Ten Eyck Hotel, Albany, 05/28/1952
  - Speeches, 10.41 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - a. State Assessors' Assn by Lt. Governor Moore. Albany, N.Y., 04/24/1952; 5 copies
    - b. N.Y.S. College for Teachers. Edward H. Butler Library. Buffalo, N.Y., 05/16/1952; 6 copies
    - c. Public Administration Society. Aurania Club. Albany, N.Y., 05/13/1952
    - d. N.Y.S. Citizens Council. Cazenovia Junior College. Cazenovia, N.Y., 06/16/1952
    - e. National Educational Association. G.G. Knoll's Laboratory Bldg. Schenectady, N.Y., 06/27/1952
    - f. Girls State - Assembly Chambers Capitol. Albany, N.Y., 06/27/1952
    - g. Johnson Coty's 60th Anniversary, 07/05/1952
    - h. Station W S N Y - Schenectady, N.Y., 07/09/1952
    - i. Station W E B R. Buffalo, N.Y. - Tape Recording, 07/24/1952
    - j. New York State Fair, Syracuse, N.Y., 09/05/1952
    - k. N.Y.S. Council of Retail Merchants at the Hotel Sagamore. Lake George, n.Y., 09/08/1952
    - l. New York State Assn. of Town Superintendents of Highways, Inc. Rochester, N.Y. - Powers Hotel Banquet, 09/18/1952
    - m. Port of New York Authority Lincoln Tunnel - third Tube - Luncheon at Astor Hotel, 09/25/1952
    - n. Woodmen's Day, Tupper Lake, 08/09/1952
    - o. Inst. At Binghamton Conference at Board of Supervisors, 09/30/1952
    - p. Men's Club of Kenmore Presbyterian Church. Kenmore, N.Y., 10/07/1952
    - q. Columbian Republican League Unity. Moore's Restaurant (Dinner). Albany, N.Y., 10/13/1952
    - r. Allegany County Village Officers Assn. Almond, N.Y., 10/15/1952
  - Speeches, 10.42 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - a. Scarsdale - Greenville Republican Club Rally. Auditorium Edgemont School, 10/20/1952
    - b. Warrensburg - Women's Republican Club Luncheon. Colonial Hotel, 10/18/1952
    - c. Schenectady - Independent Citizens Committee for Eisenhower - Support of Schen. Co. Republican Committee, 10/18/1952
    - d. Meeting of Republican Committee Men. Court House - Belmont, N.Y., 10/15/1952
    - e. Port Jervis Republican Club. Minisink Hotel - Dinner, 10/22/1952
    - f. Youth Day at State Grange Methodist Church - Saratoga Springs, 01/28/1952
    - g. Testimonial Dinner for Mrs. Caroline K. Simon, Hotel Delmonico, 10/29/1952; 2 copies
    - h. Schenectady - Dinner Meeting of the Mohawk Valley Towns Association, The Knolls, 11/10/1952
    - i. Orchards Oark - Luncheon Meeting. Niagara Frontier Milk Co-operative Bargaining Agency, 11/11/1952
    - j. Long Island Association. Gardent City, Garden City Hotel, 11/18/1952
    - k. Chautauqua County Supervisors. Hotel Jamestown (Dinner). Jamestown, N.Y., 11/21/1952
    - l. Directors of Associated Industries. Meeting at Waldors - Astoria, New York City, 12/03/1952
    - m. Schenectady Rotary Club. Luncheon. Schenectady, N.Y., 12/04/1952
    - n. Buffalo Rotary Club Luncheon. Buffalo, N.Y., 12/11/1952
  - Speeches, 10.43 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - a. University at Buffalo Round Table Moderator - WBEN TV, 01/03/1952
    - b. St. Anthony's Holy Name Society. Batavia, N.Y., 01/04/1953
    - c. Newspaper Conference in FCM's Office. Re Bond Issue for School Construct, 01/15/1953
    - d. Dedication of School 26. Buffalo, N.Y. - Sunday Afternoon, 01/25/1953
    - e. N.Y.S. Bar Assn. Municipal Law Sect. Bar Building, Thursday A.M., 01/29/1953
    - f. Association of Towns Ann. Dinner. Hotel Statler, N.Y.S., 02/04/1953; 2 copies
    - g. County Officers Assn. Convention. Hotel Syracuse. Syracuse, N.Y., 02/23/1953; 2 copies
    - h. Buffalo, N.Y. Testimonial Dinner for Roy Brockett at Y.M.C.A., 03/05/1953
    - i. Ground Breaking Ceremonies - Downstate Medical Center. New York City, 04/09/1953
    - j. N.Y.S. School for Assessors. Hotel Seneca. Rochester, N.Y., 04/23/1953
    - k. Citizens Union of City of N.Y. Hotel Roosevelt, N.Y.C., 04/27/1953; 3 copies
  - Speeches, 10.44 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - a. National Women's Republican Club. Luncheon at their club in NYC, 04/28/1953
      (see Buffalo Rotary folder 12/11/52).
    - b. Whiteface Memorial Light Dedication. Ski Lodge - Luncheon. Wilmington, N.Y., 05/31/1953
    - c. Elmira College Commencement Speech. Elmira, N.Y. (A.M), 06/08/1953; 3 copies
    - d. Welfare Officers School, At Hobart College. Geneva, 06/15/1953
    - e. New York Public Welfare Association. Lake George. Sagamore Hotel, 06/22/1953
    - f. Council of State Governments (NYC) Conference on Social Welfare and Non-Support Sponsored by NYS Leg. Comm. Interstate Co-OP, 07/10/1953
    - g. Piercefield, Boy Scout Camp. Massawepie, 08/01/1953
    - h. Erie Co. Republican $50.00 Dinner Remarks for Introducing Sinclair Weeks. Hotel Statler, Buffalo, N.Y., 09/10/1953
    - i. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y. - N.Y.S. School Boards Assn. Inc. Conv. Hall of Onon. Co Auditorium, 10/26/1953
  - Speeches, 10.45 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - a. Speech - Flushing, N.Y. Central Queens Allied Civic Council - Queens College, 10/08/1953; 6 copies
    - b. Speech - New York City - Regional Plan Ass. Hotel Roosevelt, 10/06/1953; 6 copies
    - c. Speech - Richmond, VA. Panel - More Responsible States, National Municipal League, 11/10/1953
    - d. National Municipal League. Richmond, VA, 11/1953
    - e. Speech - New Orleans, La. Session on Mun. Revenue Policies, American Municipal Association, 12/01/1953
  - Speeches, 10.46 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - a. Speech - Buffalo and Erie Co. planning Ass. Luncheon, Hotel Statler, 12/11/1953; 5 copies
  - Speeches, 10.47 (Box 46 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
    - a. Speech - Chicago, IL. Citizens of Greater Chicago. Luncheon - University Club, 01/19/1954
    - b. Speech - New York City. N.Y. Chap. Of the American Society for Public Admn. - Dinner - Hunter College, 01/27/1954
    - c. Speech - Troy, N.Y. Third Dist. Veterans of Foreign Wars. Hendrick Hudson Hotel - Dinner, 01/28/1954
    - d. Speech - New York City. Association of Towns - Annual Meeting, 02/08/1954; 3 copies
    - e. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Lawyers Club of Buffalo - annual Dinner in honor of Judge Desmond & F.C. Moore, 02/11/1954; 4 copies
    - f. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. County Officers Association Mid - Winter Conference, Hotel Statler, 02/23/1954
    - g. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y. Meeting re Equalization Rates - Chamber of Commerce Office, 03/10/1954
  - Speeches, 10.48 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. Pennsylvania Economy League. Harrisburg, PA, 03/12/1954
    - b. Speech - Chicago, IL. American Society for Public Admin. Luncheon Meeting - Conrad Hilton Hotel, 03/19/1954; 5 copies
    - c. Speech - Chicago, IL. American Society for Public Admn. Panel of Intergovernmental Relations, 03/21/1954
    - d. Buffalo Advertising Club. Buffalo, N.Y., 03/23/1954
    - e. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Meeting re Equalization Rates. Hotel Statler, 03/29/1954
    - f. Speech - Schenectady, N.Y. Brackett Lecture - Practical Politics. Union College, 03/31/1954; 5 copies
  - Speeches, 10.49 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
    - a. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y., N.Y.S. Assessors Association - Hotel Syracuse, 04/13/1954; 7 copies
    - b. State Charities Aid Association. Albany, N.Y., 04/22/1954
    - c. Speech - Jordan, N.Y. - testimonial Dinner for Fritz Campbell, Jordan High School Cafeteria, 04/22/1954
  - Speeches, 10.50 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
    - a. Speech - Albany, N.Y. Annual Spring Conference - State Charities Aid Association, 04/22/1954
  - Speeches, 10.51 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y. Allied Printing Trades Council. Annual Dinner - Hotel Syracuse, 06/23/1954; 2 copies
    - b. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Luncheon Meeting - Exec. Comm. Of Buffalo and Erie Co. Planning Assn, 06/30/1954
    - c. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Dinner Meeting - Citizens Committee for the Improvement of Buffalo, 06/30/1954
    - d. Speech - Buffalo. District Convention of Kiwanis, 09/15/1954; 5 copies
    - e. Speech - Jackson, Miss. Mississippi Research Clearing House. Luncheon Meeting - Hotel Heidelburgh, 04/28/1954
  - Speeches, 10.52 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - a. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Conference on Local Govt. of U.S. Law School. Buffalo Athletic Club, 04/30/1954
    - b. Speech - Lake Placid, N.Y. Adirondack Association. Lake Placid Club, 05/05/1954; 3 copies
    - c. Speech - Albany, N.Y. Dinner for William J. Dougherty - Dewitt Clinton Hotel, 05/17/1954
    - d. Speech - Watertown, N.Y. Joint Meeting - NYS Welfare Conference and Watertown Rotary Club - Hotel Woodreuff, 05/19/1954
    - e. Speech - Indian Lake, N.Y. Memorial Day Services, 05/31/1954
    - f. Speech - Albany, N.Y. American Statistical Assn. - Albany Chap. Assembly Chamber, State Capitol, 06/04/1954
    - g. Town Superintendents of Highways. Albany, N.Y., 09/16/1954
    - h. Speech - Philadelphia. Annual Conference of Association of Metropolitan Regional Organizations, 09/25/1954
  - Speeches, 10.53 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - a. Speech - Binghamton. Harpur College Groundbreaking Ceremonies - Introduction of Gov. Dewey, 10/06/1954
    - b. Speech - Buffalo. Introduction of Irving M. Ives. Luncheon - Hotel Lafayette, 10/16/1954
    - c. Speech - New York City. Cornerstone Ceremony - College of Medicine of New York City, 10/21/1954
    - d. Speech - West Point. Conference for Community College Trustees, 10/26/1954
    - e. Speech - Binghamton. Harpur College Groundbreaking Ceremonies - Introduction of Gov. Dewey, 10/06/1954
    - f. Speech - Buffalo. Introduction of Irving M. Ives. Luncheon - Hotel Lafayette, 10/16/1954
    - g. Speech - New York City. Cornerstone Ceremony - College of Medicine of New York City, 10/21/1954
    - h. Speech - West Point. Conference for Community College Trustees, 10/26/1954
    - i. Speech - Hotel Roosevelt. The Association of Governing Boards of St. Universities & Allied Instit, 11/16/1954
    - j. Association of Colleges and Universities of New York State, 11/12/1954; 4 copies
    - k. Speech - Kansas City. National Conference on Government - Panel on the Urban County, 11/09/1954
    - l. Governmental Research Association. Shawnee, Penna, 12/14/1954
  - Speeches, 10.54 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - a. Commencement, NYC Community College. Brooklyn, N.Y., 01/27/1955
    - b. Speech - New York City. N.Y.S. Bar Assn. - Municipal Section "Trends In local Government", 01/27/1955
    - c. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Association of Towns Annual Meeting. Hotel Statler, 02/08/1955; 4 copies
    - d. Speech - Albany, N.Y. County Officers' Association. DeWitt Clinton Hotel, 02/24/1955; 4 copies
  - Speeches, 10.55 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - a. Speech - Chicago, Ill. American Association of Junior Colleges - Sherman Hotel, 03/04/1955; 8 copies
    - b. Speech - New York City. N.Y.S. Assn. of Junior Colleges - Presentation of Award to Dean Jarvie, 03/19/1955
    - c. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y. Meeting of Councils of State University of New York - Hotel Syracuse, 05/20/1955
  - Speeches, 10.56 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - a. Speech - New York City. Inauguration of Dr. Bethel. Fashion Institute of Technology, 04/27/1955
    - b. Speech - Albany, N.Y. N.Y.S. Assessor's Association's Annual School - Hotel Ten Eyck, 04/18/1955
    - c. Speech - Brooklyn, N.Y. Brooklyn College Commencement, 06/05/1955
    - d. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. - Conference of Mayors, 06/15/1955
    - e. Speech - Glens Falls. Allied Printing Trades Council. Annual Meeting - Hotel Queensbury, 06/22/1955
  - Speeches, 10.57 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - a. Seattle, Washington. National Municipal League Conference, 07/26/1955; 7 copies
    - b. Erie Co. Technical Institute - Commencement. Buffalo, N.Y., 08/03/1955
  - Speeches, 10.58 (Box 47 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
    - a. Speech - Atlantic City. Annual Meeting - Council of State Chambers of Commerce, 09/09/1955
    - b. Speech - Cooperstown, N.Y. State University Unit Heads. Otsego Hotel, 09/25/1955
    - c. Speech - Geneseo, N.Y. Dinner Meeting of Community Leaders of Geneseo, Brockport, etc., 10/12/1955
    - d. Speech - New York City. National Association of Assessing Officers, 10/17/1955
    - e. Speech - Rochester, N.Y. New York State Grange Annual Meeting, 10/26/1955
  - Speeches, 10.59 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. Rochester, N.Y. Boy Scout Camp at Massawepie - (notes), 11/01/1955
    - b. Speech - Glens Falls, N.Y. Community College and Technical Institute Boards of Trustees, 11/03/1955
    - c. Speech - Oneonta, N.Y. State University Civic Dinner. Oneonta Teacher's College, 11/21/1955
    - d. Speech - Washington, D.C. WHC "How Can We Finance Our Schools -- Build and Operate Them?", 11/30/1955; 6 copies
    - e. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. State University Civic Dinner. Buffalo Teachers College, 12/06/1955
    - f. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. Albert Einstein College of Medicine. Fund Raising Dinner, 12/07/1955
  - Speeches, 10.60 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
    - a. Speech - Chicago, Illinois. National Association of Home Builders Annual Conv. & Exposition, 01/25/1956
    - b. Speech - N.Y.C. New York State Bar Association, 01/27/1956
    - c. County Officers Association. Statler Hotel - New York City, 02/23/1956
    - d. East Lansing, Michigan. National Conference on Metropolitan, 4/29-5/2/1956
    - e. White Sulphur Springs. Investment Bankers Association, 05/16/1956
  - Speeches, 10.61 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
    - a. Rye, New York. Westchester County Association, 05/17/1956
    - b. Rochester. Testimonial Dinner for W. Earl Weller, 05/21/1956
    - c. Washington, D.C. - Municipal Finance Officers Association. (Panel Discussion), 06/04/1956
  - Speeches, 10.62 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Oneonta - New York. State Teachers College Commencement, 05/10/1956
    - b. Garden City - Adelphi College 60th Commencement, 05/13/1956
    - c. Spokane, Washington. Pacific Northeast Assembly on State Government, 05/22/1956
  - Speeches, 10.63 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - a. Asheville., North Carolina. American Municipal Association Luncheon Meeting, 07/09/1956
    - b. Staten Island, N.Y. Opening Ceremony of Staten Is. Community College and Installation of Pres. Willig, 09/17/1956
    - c. County Officers Association. Grossinger's Liberty - NY (Monticello), 10/02/1956
  - Speeches, 10.64 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - a. Buffalo - NYS Historical Association, 10/12/1956
    - b. Rye, N.Y. - Governmental Research Association, 10/16/1956
    - c. NYC - Biltmore Hotel. Empire State Chamber of Commerce Bd of Directors - Luncheon Meeting, 10/17/1956
  - Speeches, 10.65 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - a. New York City - Eastern States Regional Conference of American Society for Public Admins, 1/19-20/1956
    - b. Princeton, N.J. Tax Institute Symposium on Financing Highways, 11/08/1956
    - c. Memphis. National Municipal League - Annual Conference, 11/11-14/1956
    - d. New York City - Hobart Club of New York (Dinner Toastmaster), 11/16/1956
  - Speeches, 10.66 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - a. St. Louis - American Municipal Association, 11/25/1956
    - b. Chicago - Assembly of the States (panel on Metropolitan Problems), 12/07/1956
    - c. Washington, D.C. - National Association of Home Builders, Newspaper contest, 12/8-9/1956
  - Speeches, 10.67 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - a. New York City - Municipal Section, State Bar Association, 01/23/1957
    - b. Buffalo, N.Y. - Association of Towns Annual Meeting, 02/12/1957
  - Speeches, 10.68 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - a. Special Studies Project in New York (Discussion), 02/20/1957
    - b. Buffalo, N.Y. - Buffalo Club Award (Luncheon), 02/22/1957
    - c. Syracuse, N.Y. - County Officers Association - Annual Meeting, 02/26/1957
  - Speeches, 10.69 (Box 48 (10-Speeches), Folder 11)
    - a. Syracuse, N.Y. Opening Session 1967 Conference on Assessment ADM, 04/01/1957
    - b. Remarks by FCM before Associated Industries - At Buffalo, 05/01/1957
    - c. Buffalo, N.Y. Buffalo Rotary Club, 05/02/1957
    - d. Hugh P. Baker Laboratory Dedication. College of Forestry - Syracuse University, 05/03/1957
  - Speeches, 10.70 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. 3rd Annual Wherrett Lecture on Local Gov't at University of Pittsburgh, 05/07/1957
    - b. Albany, N.Y. Annual Dinner of the Albany Torch Club, 06/03/1957
    - c. Brooklyn, N.Y. Remarks made by Mr. Moore at the Basic Sciences Building - Downstate Medical Center. Dedication Ceremonies, 06/08/1957
    - Rochester, N.Y. League of Women Voters of New York 27th State Convention, 05/08/1957 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 2)
  - Speeches, 10.71 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 3)
    - a. Remarks made by Mr. Moore at the Putnam Valley Central School Commencement, 06/21/1957
    - b. Buffalo Club. Remarks by Mr. Moore, Luncheon - Mr. Diebold, 06/27/1957
    - c. Speech (Outline) Given Before County Officers Association Conference. Lake Placid, N.Y., 9/27-28/1957
    - d. Speech (Notes) Fashion Institute of Technology. New York, N.Y., 10/09/1957
    - e. Speech - Board Meeting of State University at Oyster Bay, Long Island, 10/10/1957
    - f. Speech - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey. Syracuse, N.Y., 10/11/1957
    - g. Speech - International City Managers Assn - Washington, D.C., 10/21/1957
  - Speeches, 10.72 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 4)
    - a. Mr. Moore's Remarks. Hotel Delmonicio, N.Y.C. American Jewish Committee (SUBI), 10/22/1957
    - b. Mr. Moore's Remarks. Buffalo State College for Teachers, Ralph Peo (SUBI), 10/28/1957
    - c. Remarks - Arden House - N.Y. State Assn of Councils & Chests Citizens Councils Conference, 11/05/1957
    - d. Remarks. New York City, Meeting with Veterans, 11/15/1957
    - e. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y. Civil Service Employees Association, 11/21/1957
    - f. Saranac, N.Y. School Superintendents Annual Meeting, 09/17/1957
    - g. Speech - George Deming at Hot Springs, Arkansas - Meeting of Council of State Governments, Executive Committee, 12/06/1957
  - Speeches, 10.73 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 5)
    - a. Speech (Outline) - Citizens Public Expenditure Survey - Hotel Statler - N.Y.C., 01/10/1958
    - b. Speech - Municipal Law Section, N.Y.S. Bar Assn. - Hotel Commodore, N.Y.C., 01/30/1958
    - c. Speech - New York, N.Y. by Frank C. Moore at Assessors Group Annual Meeting Association of Towns, 02/10/1958
    - d. Speech - Anniversary Luncheon - Association of Towns. Hotel Commodore, Toastmaster, 02/12/1958
    - e. Speech - Buffalo, N.Y. County Officers Association, 02/25/1958
    - f. Speech - Philadelphia, P.A. National Health Forum, 03/18/1958
  - Speeches, 10.74 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 6)
    - a. Speech - Albany, N.Y. State University Faculty Senate - Brubacher Hall, 03/28/1958
    - b. Speech - New York, N.Y. American Press Institute - Seminar on Municipal Problems, Columbia University, 05/07/1958
    - c. Remarks - New York, N.Y. at 22 W 55th Street. Meeting with Students, Maxwell School of Citizenship, 05/05/1958
    - d. Speech - Brooklyn, N.Y. Inauguration - Dr. Robert A. Moore, President Downstate Medical Center, 05/02/1958
    - e. Oswego, N.Y. - Commencement, State Teachers College, 06/09/1958
  - Speeches, 10.75 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 7)
    - a. New York, N.Y. - Real Property Tax Committee and Industry Assn, 05/10/1958
    - b. Syracuse University - School for Supervisors, Maxwell School of Citizenship, 05/17/1958
    - c. Columbus, Ohio. Community Council Leaders Conference - Ohio State University, 05/21/1958
  - Speeches, 10.76 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 8)
    - a. Speech - Endicott, New York. Dedication at Harpur College, 10/02/1958
    - b. Speech - Syracuse, N.Y. Faculties Assoc. of State University Conference, 10/09/1958
    - c. Gossinger, N.Y. Conference State university Community College Trustees, 10/20/1958
    - d. Speech - Morrisville, N.Y. Dedication - AG. & Tech. Institute, 10/28/1958
  - Speeches, 10.77 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 9)
    - a. Council of Social Agencies, Westchester County. White Plains, New York, 11/10/1958
    - b. Speech - White Plains Mat'L. Talk On County Reorganization, 11/10/1958
  - Speeches, 10.78 (Box 49 (10-Speeches), Folder 10)
    - a. N.Y.C. Municipal Law Section, Belmont Plaza, 01/29/1959
    - b. New York, N.Y. Association of Towns Commodore Hotel, 02/09/1959
    - c. Buffalo, N.Y> State University College for Teachers at Buffalo dormitory dedication, 04/20/1959
  - Speeches, 10.79 (Box 50 (10-Speeches), Folder 1)
    - a. Delhi, New York. Open House at Delhi Agricultural and Technical Institute, 05/02/1959